

John Clark Blockchain Full Stack Developer

About Me

- 4 years of blockchain experience

From Launching token to DEFI, I have deep experiences in blockchain industry. Have succeeded in delivering tokens, and make social events with it on several companies. Now researching cutting-edge technology on blockchain using Golang and Rust to implement L2 Networks.

- 6 years of full stack experience

I quickly help startups and enterprises with prototypes and ideas by efficiently building those things into reality. I specialize in JavaScript and TypeScript frameworks including React, Next, and Node as well as cloud services including AWS and Azure.

Professional Skills

Blockchain	Node.js
Solidity	Python
Web3	React.js

Work Experience

Blockchain & Backend Engineer at Harvest Finance

Oct 2021 - Present

Harvest Finance is one of the largest DEFI Platform which provides the Yield Farming with most of the tokens on several networks.

- Build Smart Contract for MasterChef Staking Platform to provide rewards for holders.
- Build Smart Contract for Swap Router & Factory to implement DEX and Yield Farming with collaborating with other DEFIs.
- Update and Manage Assets for Tokens, Pools and Vaults on Backend Store.
- Build API for getting TVL, APY, and Price info for All Farms and Tokens using GraphSQL.

Skills: Solidity, DEFI, Web3, GraphQL

Blockchain Developer at Bunzz

Nov 2019 - Sep 2021

Bunzz is a Smart Ecosystem for Smart Contracts on All kinds of Blockchain Industry.

- Research Smart Contracts with Open-Source Libraries on Popular Ecosystems.
- Build Smart Contracts for ERC20, NFT, DEFI and DAO systems.
- Audit Smart Contract and build Documents for newly added contract on the Platforms.
- Supporting Projects for using the Platforms and customize Smart Contract for Clients.

Skills: Solidity, CrossChain, Audit, Al

Full Stack Engineer at StarStock

Jul 2017 - Oct 2019

StarStock is a nationwide, one stop shop for licensees to order drink and food online.

- Make an ecommerce storefront and admin application for retailers and brand owners.
- Build a common component library as a Github submodule which boosted the performance and productivity of the team more than double.
- Translate hundreds of pages from Figma design into React components using a component library for the consistency.
- Integrate several payment providers including sagepay and stripe.

Skills: React, Next, Node, Payment Integration

Education

Bachelor of Science (with Honors) Degree in Computing from University of London

2014 - 2017